

PERSONAL DETAILS

- Name
 Aimar Goñi
- **Phone number** +34688911739
- **Email** elgoni64@gmail.com
- Date of birth 14/10/2002
- **†∔ Gender** Male
- Mationality
 Spanish
- ChinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/aimar-go%C3%B1i-9a3301227/
- □ Website
 https://aimar-goni.github.io/

SKILLS

C++

C#

С

SQL Al

algorithms

team player

Git

<u>Perforce</u>

API

Computer Science

Unity

Unreal Engine
OpenGL

AIMAR GOÑI



ME

My name is Aimar Goñi, and I'm a Games development student trying to get into the games industry. I have ample experience programming, and I have even released a game to Steam called LOW BATT working in a semi-professional environment. I have also programmed my own game engine, and I have good knowledge of optimization and low-level programming.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Sep 2023 - Jul 2024

LOW BATT | AI PROGRAMMER

Watermill Studios, Valencia, Spain

Classic top-down shooter developed in Unreal Engine 5, published on Steam on July 2023. As our biggest university project, I worked alongside seven game artists, two game designers and eight game programmers. The project was supervised by two experienced game producers with whom we held regular scrum meetings. I was primarily responsible for most of the game AI. I did a full implementation of the enemies like the base programming, custom movement and evasion algorithms and the animation and particle implementation

Sep 2023 - Jun 2024

ENGINE AND GRAPHICS PROGRAMMER

VORPAL ENGINE, Valencia, Spain

Graphics Engine written from scratch in C++ & OpenGL. It runs scenes in VR headsets, implements portals, scene saving, an ECS, a user-friendly editor, and edit/play mode di{erentiation.



EDUCATION

Oct 2021 - Jul 2024

High National Diploma in Computing

ESAT - Escuela Superior de Arte y Tecnología, Valencia, Spain,

Valencia

Sep 2024 - Present

Games Development BSc

UCA - University for the Creative Arts, Farnham, UK